♪The night wind shakes off
the withered leaves♪
♪I open the window and gaze at the moon♪
♪Haze spreads across the river,
lanterns drifting♪
♪I hear the memories rustling♪
♪Garden flowers shed petals one by one♪
♪Candlelight flickers,
swaying with melancholy♪
♪I sigh by the lamp over the long night♪
♪Past memories unfold scene by scene♪
♪It's all your face♪
♪Boldly trampling over my heart♪
♪Two measures of ink I take,
one for love miswritten♪
♪And another for youth passed♪
♪With endless sorrow,
I once traced your silhouette♪
♪Two measures of ink I take,
one for joy and sorrow♪
♪And another for parting and reunion♪
♪I write until splendor fades,
and I am no more♪
=Prelude of the White Snake=
=Episode 3=
These should be enough.
Suzhen, smile.
You'll scare people off with that frown.
I can't smile right now.
Just smile a little.
Suzhen, the more sincere you are,
the easier it is to touch people.
Just being sincere is enough.
Just like this.
Young Master Xu,
for your hand injury,
I went all over the city
to buy the medicine.
Now, I'm giving these
to you.
Alright, Qing.
Your turn.
No, Qing, I can't do it.
No, I can't.
- Suzhen.
- Not at all.
Listen to me.
Young Master Xu,
my uncle has wanted
to reclaim this house.
If not for my mediation,
you would've been kicked out.
Now, I have a solution for you.
This house is where my parents lived.
It means a great deal to me.
If you have a solution,
please tell me.
When speaking to me, he looks so bitter,
but he's so gentle with this young lady.
He treats you like that?
Not really.
Young Master Xu,
if you become my husband,
my uncle will have no reason
to kick you out.
Miss Lin,
please mind yourself.
Don't you know my feelings?
Since you won't obey me,
then pack your things and get out.
What are you waiting for?
Quick, help me up.
It's you.
You're quite popular, Young Master Xu.
First Wang Erya,
then Miss Lin, and then...
What are you doing here?
Weren't you injured?
I specially went all over the city
to get medicine for you...
Thank you for caring.
I don't deserve your kindness.
Please go back.
Xu Xian.
I just saw Miss Lin.
Is that old wretch Master Lin
trying to kick you out again?
Come home with me.
Don't take their nonsense.
None of your concern.
Xu Xian,
come home with me.
Suzhen, Xu Xian's parents are both gone.
By reason, shouldn't he
cherish his only family more?
What's with his attitude?
(Xu Xian, you killed
my sister yesterday.)
(Today, I will make you taste the pain
of losing a loved one.)
Suzhen, come.
You're hurt?
It's nothing.
You're a demon hunter too?
Cut the crap.
You hurt my sister.
I'll make you pay back tenfold.
(Qing,)
(return quickly.)
How dare you come?
You're courting death!
(Spirit)
You two fox demon sisters
kill innocent people.
You should pay with your lives.
Xu Xian, you've made too many enemies.
Even if I die,
there will always be those
who come for you.
One day,
you will lose your kin
and your beloved
and live in misery.
Where did they go?
"Qing and I will escort your aunt home.
You can rest assured."
Suzhen, I've finished writing.
Qing,
your handwriting
is even worse than mine.
Let's use mine.
Not bad looking,
but her handwriting
is really something else.
This house is where my parents lived.
It means a great deal to me.
If you have a solution,
please tell me.
Young Master Xu,
why won't you look at me?
Here, let me toast you.
No need.
You said it's about the house.
That's why I came.
But the matter of the house
is entirely up to me.
Miss Lin, please show some restraint.
You keep mentioning restraint.
I'm fine with myself.
If you still want
to talk about the house,
drink this cup of wine,
and then I'll start talking business.
Can we talk now?
Young Master Xu,
am I beautiful?
Put your clothes on.
Young Master Xu.
Don't you feel hot all over now?
Need my help?
You've brought this
on yourself, you know.
Are you two honored guests
from the capital?
My surname is Zhang.
Today, I am passing through
with my wife.
Master Lin, I heard you have
a feng shui treasure land.
Are you referring to
my old house in the suburbs?
Exactly.
My husband has always
loved peace and quiet
and favored natural scenery.
If the price is right...
We can talk.
But there are quite a few people
wanting to buy that property now.
The price can't be too low.
At least five hundred taels.
It can't go lower.
Deal.
So straightforward?
Of course, I am.
However, I can only pay
one hundred taels of silver first.
For the remaining silver,
I'll use this jadeite instead.
T-This is jadeite
from Nanxiang House in the capital.
So you're willing to go through
with this deal, Master Lin?
Yes, of course.
Seeing is believing.
I'll get the deed for you two right now.
Suzhen, once we get the deed,
Xu Xian will surely obey you.
Please.
(Sign and seal)
How could my uncle
sell the house to you?
Like it or not,
you have to accept it.
From today onward,
this house belongs to Xu Xian.
You've seen the deed.
Now can you get out?
You... you two.
♪I also gave my youth to someone♪
♪I must admit, you made the journey♪
♪When loving you
became instinct, what's left♪
♪Seals a fate too brutal to amend♪
♪Clumsy and new, we gave our first kiss♪
♪Never thought passionate eyes
would turn cold♪
♪I thought of pulling away,
but I'd barely begun♪
♪Having loved you so deep,
how could I love another♪
♪Even if we're strangers again,
why deny we loved♪
♪Though I'm stubborn,
I never stopped you from loving others♪
♪I shouldn't have been so foolish
to think there was still hope♪
♪But you won't even admit what we had♪
♪Even if we're strangers again,
why deny we loved♪
♪Though I have questions,
I never questioned you♪
♪I'll lock you away and set myself free♪
♪After all, I'm the one you deny♪
♪Having ever loved♪